casinorewardclub.com 2019-03-25

# BEST ONLINE CASINOS

This privacy policy has been executed to inform and serve those customers of the website who may be concerned about exactly how their personal information may be used online. Please read this privacy policy carefully in order to obtain a clear and accurate understanding of how we collect, use, protect and/or otherwise handle your personal and personally identifiable information according to our guidelines.

**Cookies**

For the users’ information, our website DOES NOT use any cookies.

**Analytics**

Our website uses analytics such as Google Analytics in order to advertise on the Site and/or on third-party Sites to you after you visit our Site.

Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Site. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.

**The data we collect about users**

We may collect, use and store different kinds of personal data about you which we have grouped together as follows:

  * **Contact Data**  includes email address.
  * **Technical Data**  includes internet protocol (IP) address, your login data, browser type and version, time zone setting and location, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform and other technology on the devices you use to access this website.
  * **Usage Data**  includes information about how you use our website and services.
  * **Marketing and Communications Data**  includes your preferences in receiving marketing from us and your communications preferences.
